{
    "id": "359d8b1a43c547d8873b6ee04afd7071",
    "title": "Interrogative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "———————— did you do then?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e6150158d07a4565b42c53f10d338a25"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————— would you like to eat?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c07e53c53e54728ada4315a91150c77"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————- is knocking at the door?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a86ef44944f74779a62016436aae4d30"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————- is your phone number?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Which",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e7b4c1e111264050b71f13717889445e"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————– do you want to see?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Who",
                "Whom",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "3292dac4dccb4a9086a3df78cd854fd4"
        },
        {
            "question": "————————- will he say?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "How",
                "Who"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a750585f27d471aa08e3c729af48d00"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————– did you see?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Who",
                "Whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c75d426698914c2e818b08725048a8ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "About ———————– are you speaking?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "what",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "b91cb096450740e6bdf7a4172992f109"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————– came here in the morning?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whom",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a03c1888ea194e348d38f935d5062074"
        },
        {
            "question": "By ———————– was this book written?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3c8d996350ea49799e34392e5146a867"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————- do you mean?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "Why",
                "How"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7d5624abd95e4225b9d30d5f76e1b6f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————— do you think took the money?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whom",
                "Why"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f2a51f79971e45f2b2702e7031343bb5"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————– is better – wisdom or riches?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "What",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "66a9107a7c394524b6b86dd37090d085"
        },
        {
            "question": "——————– do you think is right?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Who",
                "Whom",
                "What"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "184063d1b64443b19f4e6b677f823ca6"
        },
        {
            "question": "———————— is a continent?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Which",
                "What",
                "Why"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b629a5b7d07e43f3a957db0356d175f1"
        }
    ]
}